Eunuch Jingyuan,
Eunuch Sun is dead.
I know.
You may leave.
Yes.
I didn't expect him to actually not disappoint me.
Are you okay?
It's good that you're okay.
They have all left.
Why are you still staying here?
How is your injury?
What?
Did you want to see
if I would actually die?
You're in this state,
and you can still talk back to me.
After all that effort,
only Sun Liang was dealt with.
Sun Liang was loyal to her.
I didn't expect my aunt
to be so ruthless.
But that's fine.
After today,
we won't have to live under Sun Liang's surveillance.
What are you thinking about?
Nothing.
I just suddenly felt
that Chancellor Shen is quite cute.
That's true.
Then why did you drive him away?
He clearly cared about you just now.
Since ancient times, loyal officials often die.
Rather than staying by a tyrant's side and bearing a bad name,
it's better to remain uncorrupted
and keep the people safe.
Prime Minister Shen has served two emperors.
He is the current Left Prime Minister.
Si Xinglan must have thought about winning him over.
Are you afraid that
if Prime Minister Shen really works for you,
the Grand Princess won't tolerate him?
This is obviously a virtual game.
He is obviously a virtual character.
But at this moment,
I actually feel his sorrow and helplessness.
I just simply want to change the ending for one person.
Si Xingxuan,
have you ever thought about a question?
What?
To Prime Minister Shen,
the country comes before his family.
You always play the role of an incompetent ruler and alienate him.
He will only feel that the country is ruined,
and see no hope.
As a loyal minister,
he definitely hopes to be of use.
Shen Qingyan is full of pride.
It's good enough that he didn't help the Grand Princess
to eliminate the incompetent ruler and clean up the court.
In the whole court,
who doesn't want me dead?
Even if I am willing,
he wouldn't be willing to follow me.
But if you don't try,
how would you know?
What if he is really willing to help you?
In time,
we can punch Prime Minister Zhou,
kick the Grand Princess,
and bring peace and prosperity back to Donglin.
The experiencer's character goal is 50% completed.
You two may step down first.
To think I was played by that brat.
Prime Minister Shen used to disdain His Majesty's absurd behavior the most.
Today,
he was actually willing to stay in His Majesty's bedchamber.
We cannot let him associate with Prime Minister Shen.
Doesn't he like pretending to be sick?
Then let him pretend.
In a few days,
our grand plan will be accomplished.
The Donglin empire will surely change hands.
A puppet without an heir,
let him jump around for a few more days.
Strangely enough,
whenever this kid is about to resort to violence...
As soon as he sees the fool,
he immediately calms down.
For so many years,
he actually forced himself
not to kill anyone.
This Si Xingxuan
is really not simple.
Since the Emperor cannot die right away,
isn't it easy for us to deal with that fool?
Now,
he is showing his fangs and wants to fight back.
Then we should strike where it hurts the most.
Zuoshan, you ran here to jump.
Sister Rong.
Why are you here?
I brought you a new toy.
Th-This is not a toy.
This is just a rock.
I'm not a fool.
This is no ordinary rock.
Ayan, put it in your bed to warm it up.
Once it's warm, it will turn into a puppy.
Turn into a puppy?
Turn into a puppy!
I... I want to try.
I'm so sorry, Little Prince.
Why isn't it changing yet?
A'yan can't warm it up alone.
Let me do it with you, okay?
So fast.
We need to turn it into a puppy.
A'yan.
How about we do this?
Oh, this is good.
I can't see it.
What are you doing?
Aunt, we are turning it into a puppy.
The little prince and I are truly in love.
Please grant us your blessing, Your Highness.
Change quickly, turn into a puppy.
A'yan.
How about
we go somewhere else to make puppies?
In my palace,
there are many puppies made of stones.
Go play at my place.
Oh, okay.
I want to make more puppies.
Escort the little prince.
Hurry.
Don't let the puppy get away.
Slow down.
You all saw it.
This is a royal forbidden area.
How dare these two commit such treason.
Even royal descendants,
if they damage the royal dignity,
must be punished with death.
This is the dignity of Donglin.
Yuanyuan.
I want to go see the puppy.
What are you doing?
How dare you touch the Little Prince?
Then can I touch him?
Where are you taking the Little Prince, Your Highness?
About where I take someone,
since when do I need to report to a servant like you?
Get out of my way.
I'll go see the dog first.
I'll play with you later.
Players cannot forcibly intervene in the main plot.
Designated characters can only act according to the game settings.